teamassociated.com 2017-03-16

# Privacy Policy | Team Associated

TeamAssociated.com  »  Privacy Policy

**E-mail correspondence.**  
When you send us an e-mail, we will store your communication and our reply for a time in case we correspond further. We will not share to third parties the personally identifiable information you provided us with, or sell, rent, or lease it to any third party. 

**Online form submission of comments.**  
When you send us comments through the various forms, we will store your communication indefinitely by computer backups. If we reply by return e-mail, we will store your communication and our reply for a time in case we correspond further. We will not share to third parties the personally identifiable information you provided us with, or sell, rent or lease it to any third party. 

**Online form submission of orders.**  
For your protection, the private information you submit with your order, such as but not limited to your phone number and credit card information, does not remain on the server. We will not share to third parties the personally identifiable information you provided us with, or sell, rent or lease it to any third party, except by court order. 

**Newsletter subscription.**  
When you subscribe to the Team Associated Insider's Newsletter or any other similar subscription service we offer, we use your e-mail address and any other information you give us to provide you with the information or other services you requested until you ask us to stop, or until the information or service is no longer available. You may unsubscribe at any time by following the directions in the subscribed newsletter. We will not share to third parties the personally identifiable information you provided us with or sell, rent, or lease it to any third party. 

**Cookie usage.**  
We do utilize cookies and session tracking through our website; however this is done strictly for statistical purposes and to store relevant information as you go from page to page. No personally identifiable information is stored, and the cookies do not track any information outside of the Team Associated website.
